Mash the button to
complete the heart!
Push
Hold
love
in
your
heart
Bonus confirmed!
Slightly
embarrassed
If the power of love will
reach your heart, I wish you
would stop this fighting
Sob
Haiku poem,
tanka poem
go *ie
Tremble
I can't
stand this.
Get me
the heck
out of
here.
You
two
can
enjoy
each
other's
company
without
me.
Amane
Shapely legs
All
you
need!
Beautiful Legs
Beautiful Butts
Meow Woof Meow
Hey, Hey
Daaaze
Click
Huff
Puff
Huff, puff
Akutsu
Dear Akutsu-sama
Dear Akutsu-sama,
There is something I'd like to bring to
you in person for reasons of security.
It's nothing to be suspicious of.
Please and thank you.
Fwahahaha
Has some issues
Terrible personality
Whew
Straw
Bosses these days
Insomnia
I don't wanna
do this anymore
Local Newspaper
Aieeee
Grin
grinning
Devil Chomp
Cafe Until 6PM,
Bar Afterwards